floost.com 2012-05-03

# Privacy Policy

Floost privacy policy determines how we treat your personal information while you visit the website and user our services. Your privacy is utmost important to Floost. It is important to us that our readers retain their privacy while taking advantage of the services we offer.

**Personal Information**

Floost collect personal data like email address, name, age, photo, location etc from social media like Facebook or while registering on Floost. The purpose of collecting personal data is to provide the best services at the individual level.

All the personal information collected by Floost will not be disclosed or shared with any third parties. However Floost can share required information with its partner.

**Other Information**

Floost also stores your posts, comments, feedback, and other required information to provide the service.

**Data Security**

We have taken all measures including physical, electronic and other required procedure to safeguard your data we collect online. Floost will take reasonable organizational and technical precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. Floost will take necessary action in case of theft of personal data to prevent our users but Floost will not be responsible for any loss and damage.

**Third Party Link**

Floost contains links to third party websites. Floost does not take any responsibility for the privacy policy or practices of any third parties. Subscribers or users should visit third party websites at their own risks.

**Child Protection**

We do not offer services to the children under the age of 13.  Floost will remove any information we receive from people we believe to be children under 13 from our database and cancel the corresponding accounts.

**Your choices**

Subscribers can correct, update, modify and delete their information by visiting profile update page at any time. However email address cannot be changed at a later stage.

If you opt to delete your account, your all posts will be removed from public view. However some of your information may remain on our backup media.

If you opt to deactivate your account, your all posts, comments and other related information to your account will be disabled from the public view. You can activate your account at any stage later and your all information will be restored. However FLoost does not guarantee to restore all the information as some information might be lost in the process.

**Contact US**

If you have any question regarding privacy policy or about the treatment of personal information, please write us to: [support@floost.com](http://mce_host/posting/).
